musicindiaonline.com 2004-06-02

# Music India OnLine - Privacy Policy

|   
---  

| 

### Privacy Statement for musicindiaonline.com

**musicindiaonline.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [musicindiaonline.com](http://www.musicindiaonline.com/)

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information for the purpose of constantly improving the contents of our Web site to suit the needs of our visitors. We do not use your IP address for any other purposes. 

**Advertisers**

Our Web site uses reputable third parties to serve the advertisements that you see on the pages of our Web site. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and opt-out procedures of our third party ad servers, please click here. [<http://www.maxworldwide.com/privacy_policy/>] and [<http://www.advertising.com/privacy_policy.htm>].

**Personal Information**

The personal information you provide to us viz. name, email address, etc. allows us to inform you about updates to the service and to notify you of products and services of musicindiaonline.com. We also share aggregate of these information, not individual data, with our advertisers to help them better understand our services and to monitor the reach of their advertising on the service.

We do not share, sell or use any of the identifiable personal information to any third parties under any circumstances unless we are required to do so by law.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

|
